<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CloudBees on Stephen's technical blog</title><link>https://stephenc.github.io/tags/cloudbees/</link><description>Recent content in CloudBees on Stephen's technical blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stephenc.github.io/tags/cloudbees/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Backwards compatibility</title><link>https://stephenc.github.io/post/2011-05-01-backwards-compatibility/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stephenc.github.io/post/2011-05-01-backwards-compatibility/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a tail about Jenkins (née Hudson) and Kohsuke&amp;rsquo;s policy of maintaining backwards compatibility&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back in 2006 I started working for my previous employer, just a month or two after Peter Reilly started. Initially we were working on the same team. This was a team who&amp;rsquo;s CI system was a nightly cron job that emailed off a list of failing tests to everyone&amp;hellip; obviously Peter and I had many a WTF over that old system&amp;hellip; so I convinced our boss that we should put some effort into setting up a proper CI system&amp;hellip; Initially this was CruiseControl (as he thought Hudson at version 1.64 was too new and unheard of&amp;hellip; go with the old reliable)&amp;hellip; but after a couple of pains with the CruiseControl system (monolithic xml config file), we convinced him to switch to Hudson&amp;hellip; (I don&amp;rsquo;t think we ever looked back!)&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Continuously deploy your java apps to the cloud</title><link>https://stephenc.github.io/post/2011-05-01-continuously-deploy-your-java-apps-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stephenc.github.io/post/2011-05-01-continuously-deploy-your-java-apps-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;In my previous post showed how easy it is to run your java application on CloudBees&amp;rsquo; RUN@cloud service. Today I&amp;rsquo;m going to use the CloudBees Deployer plugin for Jenkins that allows you to deploy your app to the cloud from your CI server. I am using the DEV@cloud Jenkins service for my CI infrastructure, but you can use this plugin from your own Jenkins (or Nectar) server.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So first step is to install the CloudBees Deployer plugin&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Deploy your java apps to the cloud</title><link>https://stephenc.github.io/post/2011-05-01-deploy-your-java-apps-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stephenc.github.io/post/2011-05-01-deploy-your-java-apps-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I work for CloudBees Inc., they are a great company with great products. I have mostly been working on the DEV@ side of the fence which is focused on continuous integration and basically the development side of your application, but we also have the RUN@ side of the fence where we provide a platform as a service (PaaS) for running your java web applications on the cloud. I could give you the sales pitch, but I&amp;rsquo;ll leave it at: the technologies and people behind RUN@ were one of the key reasons why I decided to join CloudBees.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>